

London, UK | tuyet.a.le@hotmail.co.uk | linkedin.com/in/toowee | github.com/toowee-le | toowee.dev

#### **SUMMARY**

A career-changer and self-taught front-end developer who turned her enthusiasm for web development into a career.

## **SKILLS**

**Programming** HTML5 • CSS3 • Sass • Bootstrap

JavaScript ES6+ • NodeJS • ExpressJS

Tools Git/GitHub • Visual Studio Code

Heroku · Netlify · WordPress

Others Project Management · Research

### **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

#### **Udacity Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree**

Mar 2020 - current

- Building 5 projects utilising HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, NodeJS, ExpressJS, Webpack, Jest and RESTful APIs
- Testing new APIs to build unique applications including a Natural Language Processing Express-Webpack app to analyse the emotions of news articles

#### **Free Code Camp**

Oct 2019 - current

 Completed 10 projects for Responsive Web Design and JavaScript Algorithms & Data Structures certifications

# Code First Girls - Introduction to Python Programming in partnership with Goldman Sachs

Feb - Apr 2020

- Worked collaboratively to learn programming fundamentals in Python using PyCharm
- Successfully built a cocktail recipe back-end app utilising
  Python and a public API as the final course project

## **Code First Girls - Introduction to Web Development**

Oct - Dec 2019

 Awarded runner-up prize for best team website built using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and Bootstrap

#### Brunel University - BSc Psychology and Sociology

Sep 2011 - Jul 2014

First Class Honours achieved

#### **PROJECTS**

## Natural Language Processing | Live Link | Github

A single-page Node Express-Webpack app that enables a computer to analyse a news article and interpret the author's emotions and perspectives using a NLP API.

Full portfolio: www.toowee.dev

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

#### **Senior Charity Administrator & Finance Officer**

Saving Faces-The Facial Surgery Research Foundation, London Mar 2017 - present

- Maintain all websites and develop web pages using semantic markup and styles built on WordPress
- Increase front-end efficiency and resolve hacking issues by switching CMS, resulting in faster content publication and increase monthly traffic by 5%-10%
- Design infographics and layouts for email campaigns and print publication for events
- Improving social media engagement by collaborating with the research team to promote new campaigns
- Directly support the CEO and Trustees in the governance of the charity and management of the administrative department of 3 people
- Improve office productivity by implementing Trello to streamline and set goals for daily operations

## **Honorary Clinical Researcher**

Saving Faces–The Facial Surgery Research Foundation, London Jan 2016 – Mar 2017

- Assisted statisticians and clinicians in managing 3 major national facial surgery clinical trials and audits
- Provided operational telephone support to over 50 hospitals for a new major NHS national audit
- Designed surveys to gather patient and public feedback

# **Lead Administrator**

Chobham Academy, London

Oct 2014 - Jan 2016

- Led parent outreach by launching and designing the weekly printed newsletter improving communication, events attendance and parental engagement
- Delegated roles to a team of 3 others to increase the efficiency of the primary school office
- Maintained the primary school's CRM